[ED]
Thank you for watching.
I'm asking the exact same question I asked last year at the big market,
They said, what kind of year was 2023?
Last year, you know, I was asking, what kind of year was 2022?
I asked, "What kind of year was 2022?
How was this year?
This year,
But it was still great.
It was the year of fulfillment. It was a serious year for me.
I was.
First of all, I wanted to win all the competitions.
That's why I won the Cinderella Festival.
I was happy,
Also,
I wanted to get buzzed,
I was able to get buzzed on purpose,
And the rest,
Everyone,
I wanted all the members to be happy,
I also wanted to make the members happy, so I thought of costumes and stuff,
I asked them and they made it for me,
So you did what you said you would do?
I thought it was very important to say out loud what I wanted to do.
What do you want to do in 2024?
In 2024...I feel that I don't want to change anything, that I don't want to change at all, but in a good way.
I don't want to change anything, not even the environment or my feelings.
I would like to see this everyday life continue as it is.
Hey...
Yes, I think so.
youtube
Yeah.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, wow.
Oh, great.
famous name
Very nice to meet you.
Oh my God, I got turned around.
I got turned around.
I turned around a lot.
toys?
No, I told him I kind of liked him, and he turned his head.
Oh, really?
Wow.
That's great.
Have your feelings changed after last year's big show and this year's big show?
Wow, yes.
A change in feelings, huh?
But my feelings toward the big market are the same every year, so in a sense they haven't changed, but of course the venue is different, so that's different.
But the venue is different, of course, so it is different.
I don't know how to say it, it's difficult.
I was on my way there, so I think I am everything.
So, yes.
Different feeling from last year.
You're asking me how I feel about that.
Hmmm...
Yes.
With a renewed spirit.
I think I was welcoming it with a desire to do more.
To today.
How was your year?
It's been a tough year.
A lot happened.
It was a really tough year.
I think we did our best.
I think it was a year of change.
I think I'm still thinking about the big one, because it's not over yet.
I think I'm still thinking about the big one.
Do you have a vague idea of what you want to do next year?
Yes, next year.
I can't really imagine it myself.
I can't really imagine the future.
I don't know what I will do last year or this year.
I don't know what will happen last year or this year.
So many things have happened.
I just can't imagine what will happen next year.
I'm sure that next year will be full of unimaginable things
I'm sure there will be a lot of unimaginable things in the coming year.
I want to make it a year of fun.
Fun is the best
There will be a lot of hard things
I know there will be a lot of things I have to overcome
I hope to make it a year in which fun comes first.
Thank you very much.
I actually celebrated this year's VTuber Ichiban, and with my honest feelings now that it's over,
Now, announcing that I'm going to do Pacifico one more time next year,
If you could say from your own mouth, what you are thinking and thinking now.
Yes, I do. What is today's concert really about?
Well, I had a lot of thoughts, but I'll say them a little bit at a time,
Well, you know, it was a brave performance. It was like a warrior's performance.
And the costumes were warrior-like,
I really felt like I was the strongest.
But, I guess, the reason I became the strongest was because I could see everyone's penlights,
I felt once again that it was the presence of everyone that made me the strongest,
There were many parts that I didn't know what kind of scenery I would see,
But when I came out, I saw the penlights of the school lunch,
I was so anxious, but when I got out there, I saw the penlights of the school lunch spreading, and everyone was looking at me with happy faces,
I was a bit nervous, but I wanted to make everyone happy,
I just wanted to make everyone happy,
That's what makes me think so.
I was glad to have met you all, and I wanted you to see the Pacifico filled to capacity,
I wanted everyone who made me feel that way to see the Pacifico filled to capacity, and I wanted to be that kind of group that makes everyone proud of my guesses.
But after today's live performance, I felt that there was nothing I couldn't do.
No matter what happens, I hope we can all look forward together, believe that it will come true, and do our best.